Marshall Westfall Collection of Photographs 6329 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marshall Westfall Collection of Photographs
1980-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marshall Westfall
6329 P
0.33 cubic feet
0.33 linear ft.
Photographs.
7513248
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 27, 2012
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
7513248
- Groups, Committees, Film Projects (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  32 Photographs.
- New Work Center and Film Project, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Flint, MI. 6 photographs.
- Example of Interviews, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  8 photographs
- Labor Conventions, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  10 photographs
- Union Presidents and Officials (Box 1, Folder 5)
  6 photographs
- 50th Anniversary of the UAW and Auto Workers Against Concessions Rally, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  April 5, 1987. Flint, MI. Sponsored by the Westfall Awareness Group. 35 photographs.
- Rallies, Demonstrations, and Protests, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  11 photographs.
- Release of Nader Book "The Big Boys", 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  May 1986, Detroit Press Club. Mike Westfall contributor to book. 2 photographs.
- General Motors Property Tax Assessment Reduction Meeting, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  October 10, 1985. Flint, MI. 7 photographs.
- Technology Conference, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  May 15, 1982. UAW Region 1-C Headquarters, Flint, MI. 7 photographs.
- Westfall CERP Technology Conference, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  October 1981. Held in conjunction with Michigan State University. UAW Region 1-C Headquarters, Flint, MI. 5 photographs